Talita Camargo

(267) 670-6315 <u>taliitacamargo@icloud.com</u> 10065 Sandmeyer Ln, Philadelphia PA, 19116

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/talita-camargo-03a40a52/ GitHub: https://github.com/taliitacamargo

Portfolio: https://taliitacamarqo.github.io/My-portfolio/index.html

Profile

Relocation Specialist and Accountant with newly acquired skills in Full-stack Development. Creative, quick-learner who enjoys learning new skills and has their sights in a full-time Web-Development position. Experienced in UI/UX Design, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery and Bootstrap.

Experience

General Manager, Caravan Transport LLC, Philadelphia, PA, Sep 2018 - Present Accounting Management

Team Management

Recognized by CEO for outstanding management and employee's productiveness.

Account Manager, Caravan Transport LLC, Philadelphia, PA Sep 2018 - Present

Relocation Specialist, Caravan Transport LLC, Philadelphia, PA Sep 2018 - Present

Relocation Specialist, Auto Run LLC Jan, Philadelphia, PA 2020 - Present

Relocation Specialist, AutoGreen INC, Philadelphia, PA Jan 2020 - Present

Auto Relocation Specialist, OX Towing LLC, Philadelphia, PA Jan 2019 - Mar 2021

Auto Relocation Specialist, GreenWay Trans INC, Philadelphia, PA Jan 2019 - Mar 2021

Relocation Specialist, Lucky Strike Express, Philadelphia, PA Sep 2020 - Nov 2020

Accounting Manager, Lucky Strike Express, Philadelphia, PA Aug 2017 - Mar 2019

Customer Service Manager, Lucky Strike Express, Philadelphia, PA Aug 2017 - Mar 2019

Education

Penn LPS Coding Boot Camp - 2021

Skills

Operations Management • Relocation • Account Management • Claims

Management • Customer Support • Dispatchers • Shipping • Leadership • Strategic Thinking • Strategy •

Projects

Quiz Challenge

https://taliitacamargo.github.io/quiz-project/index.html

Ticket Donating Web

https://taliitacamargo.github.io/project-one/

Password Generator

https://taliitacamargo.github.io/password-generator-project/index.html

Licenses & Certifications

Strategic Thinking - LinkedIn Learning

Personal Branding - LinkedIn Using Emotions to Leverage and Accelerate Change: A Guide for Leaders - LinkedIn

Decision-Making in High-Stress Situations - LinkedIn

Creative Thinking - LinkedIn Design Thinking: Data Intelligence - LinkedIn

The Art of Connection: 7 Relationship-Building Skills Every Leader Needs Now (getAbstract Summary) - LinkedIn Learning

Design Thinking: Lead Change in Your Organization - LinkedIn

Critical Thinking - LinkedIn Improving Your Listening Skills - LinkedIn

How to Make Strategic Thinking a Habit - LinkedIn

Body Language and Women at Work - LinkedIn

Prioritizing Tasks for Maximum Impact - LinkedIn

Digital Strategy - LinkedIn Communication for Product Managers - LinkedIn

Project Management Foundations: Integration - LinkedIn

Succeeding in Web Development: Full Stack and Front End - LinkedIn User interface design - California Institute of the Arts

UX Design - California Institute of the Arts Web Design - California Institute of the Arts